https://fruits-passion.com/en-ca/privacy-policy/

Menu
ShopHome & KitchenBest SellersBy CollectionCucinaAuraaloBy CategoryHand SoapFragrance for DiffusersDish DetergentAll Purpose CleanerRefillsRoom SprayPerfumed CandleHand CareBest SellersBy CollectionCucinaaloBy CategoryHand SoapNourishing ButterHand Cream & LotionRefillsBody CareBest SellersBy CollectionaloFine FragranceIn-house fragrancesBy CategoryShower GelBody CreamBody ScrubFoaming BathBath BombOilsRefillsAccessoriesFragrancesBest SellersBy CollectionaloFine FragranceBy CategoryEau de ToiletteEau FraîcheSkin CareBy CategoryMaskSetsAccessoriesPromotionsCollectionsCucinaCoriander and Olive TreeLime Zest and CypressSea Salt and Amalfi LemonSanguinelli Orange and FennelVerbena YuzuGrapefruit RhubarbPompelmoBeetroot extractBasil extractSkincareSheet MasksaloOrange CantaloupGrapefruit GuavaOcean FlowerPear PeonyIn-house fragrancesBlack RoseEucalyptus LemonLavender EssenceChampagne CuvéeAuraDiffusersSnowy ForestFrosted BirchWarm HoneyWinter BerriesVanilla and Baltic AmberCactus and DragonfruitCoconut LeavesJasmine & Rose WaterTulipFine FragranceKate
Legend:
Seasonal Fragrance
New Fragrance
Best SellersHolidayPromotionsAbout us
Privacy Policy
Confidentiality and Privacy Policy
October 16, 2015
Fruits & Passion Boutiques Inc. (hereinafter “Fruits & Passion”) is committed to ensuring the confidentiality of any information conveyed via the Internet or used in transactions at Fruits & Passion stores or on the website (the “Site”), as well as the privacy of data collected during certain commercial activities supported by Fruits & Passion, such as warehouse sales or promotional contests.
In conjunction with this confidentiality and privacy policy (the “Policy”), Fruits & Passion will disclose to you:
The security measures it has put in place to protect your personal information and data
The nature of the personal information we gather when you visit a store, use the Site and/or order products from the Site (“Personal Information”)
The reasons we gather such Personal Information, how it will be used and the persons/entities that may have access to it
Fruits & Passion reserves the right to modify this Policy at any time, effective as soon as changes are posted on the Site, with no liability to you or any other individual. If we make modifications, we will post the new Policy on the Site and indicate the date of the most recent update.
Confidentiality and Security
Fruits & Passion undertakes to uphold the confidential nature of any Personal Information that you may provide when using the Site or in another transaction.
The Fruits & Passion website and network that connects franchise stores to the head office use Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology. This means that all personal and credit card information is transmitted in the form of an encrypted electronic message that guarantees confidentiality. The message therefore cannot be intercepted, altered or decoded by a third party. In addition, Fruits & Passion servers are protected by firewall-type technology.
However, no security measure is perfect and you should be aware that there is always a certain level of risk that the Personal Information you submit to Fruits & Passion might be disclosed without your consent through no fault of Fruits & Passion. Fruits & Passion hereby waives any liability regarding the disclosure of your personal and confidential information, except in the event that such disclosure results from negligence on its part.
It is important to note that, in order to ensure security, no credit card-related data is kept on Fruits & Passion’s servers. Should you be concerned about the issue of confidentiality and the use of your credit card on the Internet, Fruits & Passion invites you to place your order by phone by calling 1-866-638-8417 and speaking with one of our representatives.
What Personal Information Does Fruits & Passion Gather?
Fruits & Passion gathers only Personal Information that you provide when in a store (through our franchisees and corporate boutiques) or when you use the Site, including specifically when you create an account, purchase products, sign up for special offer notifications, and enter promotions or contests. “Personal Information” includes your name, address, phone number, email address, gender (male/female), age/birthdate, credit card number and certain other information that you may agree to provide. In so doing, you agree that your confidential Personal Information may be gathered, used, and communicated for the purposes and events set forth in the Policy.
How Does Fruits & Passion Use My Personal Information?
Fruits & Passion may use the your Personal Information (gathered in stores, on the Site or elsewhere) to set up an account in your name, process your order, contact you in the event that you win a prize as part of a contest, provide after-sale service, offer you promotions (including by SMS if you provide your cellphone number when creating your account), personalize its communications with you and, if you so consent, to occasionally send you customized updates about the Site and its products,offers and promotions through newsletters or other forms of communication. We may also use your Personal Information for statistical purposes and as required by law, including in compliance with court orders.
Unless you expressly authorize it, Personal Information gathered in stores (through our franchisees and corporate boutiques) is used only by Fruits & Passion or its franchisees in accord with this Policy.
What Third Parties May Have Access to My Personal Information?
Your Personal Information may be shared with our affiliated companies and/or service providers that contribute to or participate in various aspects of our commercial activities and product management; they may be located throughout the world, including in countries whose policies for protecting personal information are not the same as Canada’s. More specifically, we may give your address to the shipping company responsible for delivering the products you have ordered, and the details regarding your sales transaction and credit card number will be disclosed to the card issuer. Our service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements and other legal restrictions that prohibit them from using data we provide for any purpose other than fulfilling their specific duties as subcontractors.
Fruits & Passion may also disclose your confidential Personal Information as required by law, including in compliance with court orders.
The personal information gathered on the Site will be conveyed to the aforementioned third parties only. Fruits & Passion assures you that its advertisers and/or partners do not, at any time, have access to your confidential Personal Information. Moreover, Fruits & Passion does not resell its customer list in which case Fruit & Passion will ensure appropriate confidentiality restriction are in place.
Unless we have your express permission, the Personal Information gathered in our stores (through our franchisees) will be disclosed to Fruits & Passion only.
Fruits & Passion may also disclose you Personal Information to a third party in the event of a change of ownership, or a grant of a security interest in, all or part of Fruits & Passion through, for example, an asset or share sale, or some other form of business combination, merger or joint venture or as permitted by law.
Links to Other Sites
The Fruits & Passion Site includes links to other websites operated by other companies. By clicking on these links, you will leave the Fruits & Passion Site. Fruits & Passion has neither developed, reviewed or verified the accuracy of the data contained on these sites. Fruits & Passion has no control over the operation of these websites and the fact that they may be linked to the Fruits & Passion Site does not in any way render Fruits & Passion liable, specifically as regards their content, the products/services provided or any other damages or loss that they may cause you. Any Personal Information that you transmit through these websites will be subject to their policies for the protection of personal information. We suggest that you pay close attention to the privacy policies of these websites.
Cookies
Cookies, or “telltale marks,” are small text files that embed themselves on your hard drive from some of the Site’s pages. The cookies used by Fruits & Passion are harmless in the sense that they cannot extract any information from your hard drive. In addition, you retain full control over cookies since you have the ability to remove them. Fruits & Passion uses cookies primarily to determine site traffic, convey useful information to its Marketing Department, and personalize your future visits to the Site.
The Right to Access, Correct or Remove Information, and Questions
Your Personal Information will be on our servers located in Canada.
You have the right to access, modify, correct or remove your personal information. To invoke this right, or if you have questions about the gathering, use or sharing of your Personal Information, please contact us at 1-866-638-8417 or email info@fruits-passion.com.
You may opt out of Fruits & Passion emails about the Site and products at any time by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the newsletter or modifying your settings in the “My Account” section of the Site.
Terms of use
1.1 Data collected by automatic means
Several technologies can be used on our website to make them more user-friendly, efficient and reliable. These technologies may include an automatic data collection by ourselves or by third parties on our behalf. In general, these data do not contain personal details about the user. These technologies include, in particular, cookies, Adobe Flash cookies and analytics softwares.
1.1.1 Data
A visit to one of our websites causes the browser to send data to our server. This data is automatically collected and stored by us or by others on our behalf. This data may include, in particular:
IP address of the visitor
the date and time of visit
pages visited on our website
information on the browser used (type and browser version, operating system, etc.)
1.1.2 Cookies
On our website, Cookies can be used in several places. In general, these small text files stored on the hard drive of your computer or your mobile device through your web browser. Cookies help to make our website more user friendly, more efficient and more reliable. The cookies we commonly use are "session cookies" which are automatically deleted at the end of the visit of the web site. By default, browsers allow the use of cookies, but this feature can also be disabled. However, some services may not be available. It is also possible to manually delete cookies after use, using the Web browser. Fruits & Passion is not aware of cases where Cookies reportedly damaged a computer or mobile device, or contributed to viral infection.
The following links provide detailed information on the most popular browsers:
Internet Explorer: http://support.microsoft.com/gp/cookies/en
Mozilla Firefox: http://support.mozilla.com/en-US/kb/Cookies
GoogleChrome: http://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647
Safari: http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042
Opera: http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/
1.1.3 Web Beacons and links trackers
Web beacons (also called "pixel tags" and "healthy GIF") contain graphic symbols that the user cannot see. The links trackers or similar technology consist of a few lines of code instruction and can be incorporated into our website or our application (mobile). With Cookies, they are mostly used for statistical analysis. This technology can also be used to monitor traffic patterns on websites, or to find out if an email has been received and opened, and if a response was given to it.
1.1.4 Cybermetrics
The term "cybermetrics" means a method of collecting and evaluating the behavior of Web site visitors or (mobile) applications. The latter includes the analysis of traffic patterns in order, for example, to determine the frequency of visits to certain parts of a Web site or application (mobile) or to find out what information and services most interest our visitors. To do this, we essentially use clickstream data and other techniques described above. The cybermetric data are managed by Google Analytics. You can find more information on the treatment of data by Google Analytics cybermetrics developed below.
1.2 Cybermetric Data Processing by Google Analytics
The cybermetric services used on our website and our (mobile) applications are provided by Google Analytics (www.google.com/analytics). This means that when you visit our website, a cookie Google Analytics is placed on your computer or mobile device unless the settings of your browser does not allow these Cookies (see 2.1.2 above).  Furthermore, when you visit our website, cybermetric data described previously in Chapter 1 - including "clickstream data," the data provided by "web beacons and links trackers", and the information stored in cookies Google Analytics - Google Analytics will be sent to be analyzed to Fruits & Passion.
Google Analytics operates as an agent of Fruits & Passion, which means Fruits & Passion only determines the purposes for which the data are used and that Google Analytics cannot disclose information to third parties (unless required to do so by law or by a court decision).
In terms of respect for private life, it means total Fruits & Passion is the "guarantor" and Google Analytics and the "data processing clerk." You can find more information on the relationship between Fruits & Passion and Google Analytics in Google Analytics privacy policy to "Privacy Policy" at the following address: http://www.google.com/intl/fr/policies / privacy /.
If you do not want that information about your visits to our website is collected and evaluated by Google Analytics, you can refuse it. This means that Google Analytics make anonymous information it collects (but continue to collect), or stop collecting information about your visit, depending on the type of opposition you have chosen. This opposition forces you to accept that a cookie be placed on your computer by Google Analytics. You can ask to object by clicking on the link provided for this purpose in the part of the website that contains the Google Analytics privacy policy.
(Https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
1.3 retargeting Technologies
Our website uses retargeting technologies on the Internet. Thus, visitors who are already interested in our services, can view our advertisements on partner websites. We are confident that the display of personalized advertising, based on interest, is more interesting than a publicity unrelated to the person.
We also work with companies that use tracking technologies. These companies provide advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. It is possible that these companies collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our communications, including advertising.
Retargeting technologies analyze your Cookies and display advertisements based on your Internet behavior. For more information about cookies, please see section 1 of this Privacy Policy. This technology does not record any of your personal information. In addition, the use of our retargeting technology conforms to the current requirements for the protection of applicable privacy.
You can disable the use of cookies by Google by accessing Preferences Manager announcements. You can also disable the use of cookies by a third party vendor to the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page and DoubleClick deactivation page or off page Network Advertising Initiative.
Our commitments
Biodegradableformulas
Recyclablecontainers
Ingredients of natural origin
Products not testedon animals
back
Follow us
